bizfilings.com 2009-06-16

# Incorporate: Incorporation,LLC,Nonprofit - BizFilings

| 

## BizFilings Privacy Policy

**BizFilings respects the privacy of the users of our services and Website. To that effect, we have instituted the following Privacy Policy:**

Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect your personal and business information, how we handle and protect this information, and what you can do to help protect this information. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to accurately reflect how we gather and manage your information. All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective upon posting to this Website without notice to you.

**Collection of Information**

To effectively process your order, BizFilings needs to collect some personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, and credit card number (" _PII_ "). For the purpose of forming your corporation or limited liability company (" _LLC_ ") we need to know some information about your business such as the name you want your business entity to have, a brief description of the purpose of your business, the name and address of the corporation or LLC's registered agent, the name and address of the directors and officers of your corporation, or members or managers for your LLC, how many shares of stock your corporation will be authorized to issue, and the par value of such stock (" _Business Information_ ").

Filings made with a state and/or county become a matter of public record, meaning the information included in that filing is accessible to the public. Some of the Business Information we collect from you, such as the name of your business, the legal address of the business, the registered agent name and address, names and addresses of directors and/or managers will become a matter of public record once your formation or other state/county filing documents are filed with the applicable state/county agency. If you have questions about which Business Information will become part of the public record, please contact us Monday – Friday from 8:00 AM to 7:00 PM at 800-981-7183 or 608-827-5300.

Our Website is set up to automatically collect anonymous information about visitors. For example, our Website automatically gathers a visitor’s Internet Protocol address, which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, statistics about how visitors navigate through and use our Website, and information gathered through the use of “cookies.” We use cookies to help us understand our visitors and traffic patterns to our site; to know when visitors have accessed our site from one of our paid advertisements, an affiliate website, or a strategic partner website; and to populate the order contact information for our registered resellers into our order forms to simplify their order process. We also compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our site, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our Website, and from which countries those requests come. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no PII or Business Information and cannot be used to gather such information. Our Website is not set up to automatically track, collect or distribute PII about our Website visitors.

Solely for the purposes of confirming valid traffic from certain pay-per-click search engines, IP addresses for such visitors are monitored, and may be compared to the records of that search engine.

**How We Protect and Use Your Personally Identifiable Information**

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, all PII and Business Information entered into our secure online order form is encrypted with secure server software to protect it from unauthorized access. Your PII, including your credit card information and username and password for accessing our Online Corporate Status Center will remain encrypted within our database. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number when confirming an order, although we do transmit the entire credit card number to our credit card processor during order processing.

BizFilings uses the PII and the Business Information you provide to fulfill your order and respond to customer service or support questions. We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling certain portions of orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service for certain portions of orders. They have access to the PII and Business Information only as necessary to perform their functions, and may not access or use it for any other purpose.

Sometimes, BizFilings will work with businesses we do not control to present you with a special offer for goods or services. If you order or sign up for a special offer through our Website where the goods or services are sold directly to you or directly fulfilled by another business, we will give your PII and/or Business Information to that business only as necessary to fulfill the offer and complete that order. BizFilings will not transmit your credit card information. You will be able to tell when another business is involved in a transaction. Our order form will state the name of the business that will fulfill the special offer, and you will have the chance to cancel the order before any of your PII or Business Information is transmitted to that business.

When users type information into our secure online order form, but do not complete the order process, that information, including PII, credit card information, and Business Information, is temporarily stored for three months in our encrypted database, and then permanently deleted.

We have appropriate security measures in place within our database and in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you on our Website. The measures include limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers as well as electronic security systems and password protections, which guard against unauthorized access.

BizFilings will not sell, rent or trade any of your PII, credit card or payment information, Business Information, or any other information collected during the ordering and fulfillment process to any third party for any purpose whatsoever.

BizFilings utilizes e-mail to communicate with customers regarding their orders and regarding features of certain products/services that were ordered. BizFilings may occasionally use your PII to notify you of its new services and special offers via periodic mailings or e-mail updates. Customers may opt-out of these communications. For all e-mail-based marketing communications, BizFilings utilizes a double opt-in policy in which individuals must explicitly request our e-newsletter and e-mail-based promotions not specific to their orders and then respond to a confirmation e-mail to receive them. If you are receiving these materials (either in electronic form or hard copy) and would like to be removed from our list, please send an e-mail to [marketing@bizfilings.com](mailto:marketing@bizfilings.com).

**Disclosures**

If we are required by law or legal process, we will disclose or provide access to your PII or Business Information to such government or judicial authority as specified by such law or legal process.

**Options**

Upon request we will provide customers with access to their own records. Customers can access and correct their PII or Business Information by e-mailing us Monday – Friday from 8:00 AM – 7:00 PM at [info@bizfilings.com](mailto:info@bizfilings.com), calling us at (800) 981-7183 or 608-0827-5300, or by updating certain PII and Business Information within the Online Corporate Status Center, 24/7, using the username and password provided during ordering.

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of BizFilings who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of any personal information, including PII and Business Information, to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [info@bizfilings.com](mailto:info@bizfilings.com).

If you feel that this Website is not following its stated Privacy Policy, you may contact us Monday – Friday from 8:00 AM – 7:00 PM at 800-981-7183 or 608-827-5300 or via e-mail at [info@bizfilings.com](mailto:info@bizfilings.com).

|
